SHARON SMITH

6001 Bermuda, St. Louis, Mo 63135 Home: 314-524-3098 | Cell: 314-484-2088 chinad786@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Efficient and reliable CNA with number years experience in a hospital setting. Assisted with technical nursing treatments, supported diagnostic procedures and charted resident records. Interested in a full-time role as a nursing assistant in a top-notch healthcare facility.

SKILLS

- CPR/First Aid certified
- Feeding assistance expert
- Dementia and Alzheimer's knowledge
- Trustworthy companion
- Companionship and emotional support
- Compassionate
- Compassionate caregiver
- Efficient and reliable team player
- Committed team player

WORK HISTORY

Certified Nurse Assistant

March 2011 to January 2013

Brooking Park - Lake Chesterfield, MO

- Maintained accurate records of patient care, condition, progress and concerns.
- Monitored vital signs, such as blood pressure and pulse.
- Responded appropriately to the physical, emotional and developmental needs of patients.
- Assisted patients with bathing, oral hygiene, grooming, feeding and elimination.
- Helped patients move in and out of beds, baths, wheelchairs and automobiles.
- Followed safe lifting techniques and individual resident lifting instructions.
- Answered patient calls for care and feeding.

Clinical Partner

May 2003 to January 2008

Depaul Health Center - Bridgeton, MO

- Monitored vital signs, such as blood pressure and pulse.
- Tested and recorded blood glucose levels.
- Assisted patients with bathing, oral hygiene, grooming, feeding and elimination.
- Helped patients move in and out of beds, baths, wheelchairs and automobiles.
- Assisted with patient transfer and ambulation.
- Followed safe lifting techniques and individual resident lifting instructions.
- Assisted patients with ambulation and crutch walking.
- Performed procedures and uses equipment as delegated by a licensed professional, including blood draws, foley catheter removal and EKGs.
- Answered patient calls for care and feeding.

Clinical Partner

July 1994 to May 2003

St. Joseph Health Center - Kirkwood, MO

- Monitored vital signs, such as blood pressure and pulse.
- Tested and recorded blood glucose levels.

- Assisted patients with bathing, oral hygiene, grooming, feeding and elimination.
- Helped patients move in and out of beds, baths, wheelchairs and automobiles.
- Assisted with patient transfer and ambulation.
- Followed safe lifting techniques and individual resident lifting instructions.
- · Answered patient calls for care and feeding.
- Collects patient specimens and data, including vital signs, input/output and other delegated measurements.

Certified Nurse Assistant

August 1991 to July 1994

1986

Meadowbrook Manor - Des Peres, MO

- Monitored vital signs, such as blood pressure and pulse.
- Assisted patients with bathing, oral hygiene, grooming, feeding and elimination.
- Helped patients move in and out of beds, baths, wheelchairs and automobiles.
- Answered patient calls for care and feeding.
- Collects patient specimens and data, including vital signs, input/output and other delegated measurements.

EDUCATION

Mccluer High 1980

Florissant, MO

High School Diploma: Basic Education

Vocational Training Center

Lake St Louis, MO

Certified Nurse Assistant

CERTIFICATIONS